# PORAMAT RODHONGTHONG

# Junior Software Developer

**(**+66) 97 054 4544

github.com/maipormat

<u>mai00841@hotmail.com</u>

linkedin.com/in/poramat

# PROFILE SUMMARY

Recent graduate of a Junior Software Development Bootcamp seeking a Software Developer role. With 3 years of experience as a Video Editor and Content Creator, I bring strong teamwork skills and a commitment to self-learning. Ready to apply my prior experience and newly developed technical skills to grow in the tech industry.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS
- Git GitHub
- Tailwind
- Figma
- JavaScript
- Trello
- React
- Adobe Ps,Pr,Ae,Ai
- SQL

#### SOFT SKILLS

- · Growth mindset
- Teamwork
- · Self-learning
- · Problem solving
- · Time management

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Generation Thailand**

August 2024 - December 2024

#### Participant (Junior Software Developer)

- Completed an intensive full-stack software development training program specializing in web application development using the MERN stack (React, TailwindCSS, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB).
- Designed and developed Handy Haven, an e-commerce platform for selling handmade products, using the MERN stack to create a smooth shopping experience.

# Friendstube (YouTube - Co-created with friends)

2021-2023

#### Video Editor & Content creator

- Created more than 80 videos for the Youtube channel
- Served as the main host in the channel's videos.
- Planned video shoots and developed creative concepts.

# Mega clinic

September 2022 - December 2022

#### Photographer & Video Editor

- · Shot and edited the videos for advertisement
- Collaborated on content development to drive audience engagement.

## **EDUCATION**

## King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

2017 - 2021

Applied Computer Science - Multimedia

#### Benchamarachuthit chanthaburi school

2015 - 2017

• ICTP (Information & Communication Technology Program)